start64.com 2012-06-22

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

We respect your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at our site start64.com. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site. 

##### Log Files

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

##### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Our site doesn't use cookies. However, Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. 

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 

  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 

  * 

##### Links

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

##### Advertisers

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and/or web beacons to collect data in the ad serving process and are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. We work with the ad company Google Adsense. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies. 

##### Contact Information

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:
